Santo Doni Romadhoni

Email: exblopz@gmail.com | HP/WA: 085790932477 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/romadhoni/ | Portofolio

SUMMARY

I am a PHP Programmer with over 20 years of experience, especially in backend and API development. During my career, I have worked on various projects, including e-commerce, POS, and other systems. In addition to programming, I also have expertise in copywriting, video editing, and content creation, thanks to my experience in the world of literacy.

EXPERIENCES

Senior Programmer | PT Alpha Tech Indonesiana | 01 August 2021 - Now

- Develop LMS KlasQ software for elementary, middle and high schools. The application not only supports teaching and learning activities but also provides an application for student exams. The application used is on the Android platform and website. This software has also been used by several schools in East Java.
- Develop E-Commerce software for Gab's Jeans and Gabrielle Jeans companies. This E-Commerce application is able to apply online purchases to online payments using Midtrans. Including stock systems, shipping and flash sales. Some of the developments include a return system and points from customers that can be exchanged.
- Work on several projects such as landing pages, POS software and websites.

IT Support | PT. Adhi Persada Property | 01 January 2020 - 31 May 2020

- Working on marketing software such as SMS broadcast and Whatsapp for apartment marketing.
- Developing website and landing page of Adhi Persada Property apartment project.

Senior Programmer | MGG Software, Pte Ltd | 01 January 2015 - 31 May 2019

- Develop DSS software for a military vehicle company. The application is a tool that is usually used by drivers when there is an error or malfunction. The script uses raphaelJS to create simple SVG-based vectors.
- Work on several other projects, mostly for mobile applications.

IT Support | PT. Sinar Media Tiga | 01 January 2012 - 31 Desember 2012

- Develop cashier software with simple accounting.
- Help work on the LintasGPS project, an application to create a GPS tracker application.

IT Support | Kapanlagi.com (PT. Monster Mob Indonesia) | 01 February 2008 - 31 January 2011

• Helping to work on the backend for transaction reports and several applications for content providers.

IT Support | CV. SuperSoft | 01 Januari 2006

• Develop pulsa software reload for pulsa transaction. This software made and design with PHP native and the gateway SMS using Visual Basic 6.

Pengajar Web Developer | LP3I | 01 Juli 2007

Teaches website creation material for beginners using HTML, Javascript and CSS.

EDUCATIONS

STIKOM Surabaya | D3 Manajemen Informatika

2002 - 2006

ORGANIZATIONS

Ketua Umum | Unit Kegiatan Kerohanian Islam Pradana | Pramuka SMAN 7 Kediri

2004 2001

SKILLS

- PHP, HTML, Javascript, CSS, Java, ReactJS, ExpressJS
- Framework: CI, Laravel
- Editing Video (Capcut)
- Softskill: Copywriting, Content Creator
- Editor yang biasa dipakai: Microsoft Visual Studio, Notepad++, vim
- Language : Bahasa Indonesia, Bahasa Inggris